webexpo.cz 2013-12-11

# WebExpo → Privacy Policy

We collect personal information from our customers in the regular course of doing business. The information includes 

  * Name (required)
  * E-mail address (required)
  * Twitter account
  * LinkedIn account
  * Personal website
  * City
  * Gender

Only the required information are necessary to access our full service. 

We do **not** collect financial information such as payment card number neither payment card expiry date nor credit records.  
We collect purchase history data which includes 

  * Banking information
  * Payment history
  * Order history

In order to complete your sales/transactions, manage orders and returns, administer a loyalty program and deliver services. We collect interests and hobbies such as 

  * Customer satisfaction information
  * Opinions about products and services
  * Skills in different fields of business, design and development

We collect information using application forms and social services including Facebook, Twitter, Google, LinkedIn and OpenID. We use only the necessary personal information to be able to identify and contact you. 

### Tracking technologies

We use cookies to store user's session and to provide a convenient user experience using our website. We use an external service for a traffic analysis which uses cookies as well. 

We use your personal information in order to deliver services, manage your orders and returns. We use your personal information in contests, surveys, interests and in application forms. 

If it's a necessary part of any of these transactions, we may disclose your information to another company. For example, when you apply for credit, we pass on your personal information to a credit reporting agency so we can complete a credit check. We also pass on your name and address to a courier company to complete a delivery. 

### Our Partners

Sometimes, we also share your personal information with other companies, including our accounting company and trusted partners. 

All information are stored in a digital form in a secure, password protected place. Your password is encrypted using a hashing algorithm with salt.  
Your data are stored until you delete them. 

### Contact Us

**WebExpo s.r.o.**  
Radlická 180/50  
Praha 5  
150 00  
Business ID: 24661104  
VAT ID: CZ 24661104

Email: [info@webexpo.net](mailto:info@webexpo.net)
